aussiesurveys.com.au 2011-12-24

# Great Sites

­Great Sites­­­ takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Great Sites treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you register and complete any surveys with Great Sites. This policy also covers Great Sites treatment of any personally identifiable information that Great Sites business partners share with Great Sites or vice versa.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Great Sites does not own or control, or to people that Great Sites does not employ or manage. Great Sites collects personally identifiable information when you register and/or complete surveys with Great Sites.

When you register with Great Sites, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender address, and marital status among other personal details. Once you register with Great Sites and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Great Sites uses information for two general purposes: to allow advertisers to market their products and services to you based upon your profile, and to analyse and provide analysis in aggregate form based on member profiles. This includes the use of browser cookies to display relevant ads on other websites. 

From time to time Great Sites will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people for marketing or research purposes.

  * By registering and/or completing surveys with Great Sites you are providing your consent for this to happen.  You may unsubscribe from the service at any time, which will have the effect of withdrawing your consent.

In addition we may provide your details to other companies when:

  * We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested; 
  * We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of Great Sites to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or

You may request deletion of your account with Great Sites by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link contained in every email we send you, by emailing us directly with your request, or logging into your account and using the feedback form.  If you unsubscribe from Great Sites your account will be deleted after the next prize draw and you will:

  * Not be able to earn any additional entries into the next prize draw (but your existing entries will still be valid for the next prize draw) 
  * Not be contacted by Great Sites other than for administrative purposes

  * Not have your data provided to any third party companies for marketing or other purposes

Your Great Sites account information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

In certain areas Great Sites uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

Great Sites may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
